Inventory of the Papers of Monroe Leigh, 1941 - 2001
University of Virginia, Arthur J. Morris Law Library
- International Criminal Court (ICC)
  - American Bar Association (ABA)
    - ICC: Correspondence re: ICC, 1994, 1996, 1998 (Box-folder 11 - 8)
      Contains Monroe Leigh signature, Correspondents include: Monroe Leigh, Jerome J. Shestack, John Murphy, M. Cherif Bassiouni, Maury Shenk, George E. Bushnell, Jr., Lucinda Low, Michael D. Sandler,
    - ICC: Correspondence re: ICC, November 1994 - February 1995 (Box-folder 11 - 9)
      Correspondents include Monroe Leigh, Richard L. Gaines, George E. Bushnell, Jr., Christopher Keith Hall, Willaim M. Hannay, and Stuart H. Deming
    - ICC: UN Sixth Committee and Committee on International Criminal Court Meetings, Oct 1993, April 1995, August 1995 (Box-folder 11 - 10)
      Summaries discuss efficacy, progress, establishment, and jurisdiction of a permanent ICC
    - ICC: Reports re: ICC, 1993 - 1995 (Box-folder 11 - 11)
      Contains handwritten notes
    - ICC: Press and Articles re: ICC, 1993 - 1995 (Box-folder 12 - 1)
    - ICC: Washington Working Group on the ICC Materials, 1995 (Box-folder 12 - 2)
      Contains underlining, handwritten markup, background materials on interested lobbyists, congressional politicians, presidential administrators
    - ICC: Materials related to May 18, 1995 Meeting 18 May 1995 (Box-folder 12 - 3)
      Contains handwritten pages of notes, markup, remarks, post-it notes
    - ICC: Correspondence &,amp, Notes re: establishment of ICC, 1993 - 1995 (Box-folder 12 - 4)
      Contains handwritten pages of notes, markup, correspondents including: Francisco Jose Aguilar-Urbina, Conrad K. Harper, H. E. Boutros Boutros-Ghali, Marvin E. Frankel, Michael Posner
    - ICC: Resolutions / Reports from UN &,amp, ABA, 1992 - 1993 (Box-folder 12 - 5)
      Contains post-it markers and underlines, Includes: Text of Treaty: "No. 1021. Convention on the Prevention and Punishment of the Crime of Genocide. Adopted by the General Assembly of the United Nations on 9 December 1948, UN Security Council Official Documents, ABA Reports with Recommendations to the House of Delegates of the Task Force on an International Criminal Court of the American Bar Association and the New York State Bar Association
  - ABA War Crimes Task Force - Yugoslavia
    - Contact information, 1995 (Box-folder 12 - 6)
      Contains names, addressed, phone numbers
    - 1.1 Index of Files, 2002 (Box-folder 12 - 7)
    - 1.2 Bulletin, 1996 - 2000 (Box-folder 12 - 8)
    - 1.3 CEELI, 1995 - 1998 (Box-folder 12 - 9)
      Contains handwritten notes, highlights, memos
    - 1.4 United Nations, Aug 1995 - Feb 1997 (Box-folder 12 - 10)
      Contains highlights and handwritten notes
    - 1.5 US Law, 1994 - 1996 (Box-folder 12 - 11)
      Contains markup, handwritten notes, post-it notes, highlighting
    - 1.6 Press, 1997 - 2000 (Box-folder 13 - 1)
      Contains handwritten notes, post-its, highlighting, comments
    - 1.7 Procedural Rules (a - Correspondence Materials), 1993 - 1994 (Box-folder 13 - 2)
      Contains highlights and notes
    - 1.7 Procedural Rules (b - Correspondence General/Meeting), 1993 - 1998 (Box-folder 13 - 3)
      Contains post-its and notations
    - 1.7 Procedural Rules (c - Proposed revisions/drafts), 1993 - 1994 (Box-folder 13 - 4)
      Contains edits, highlights, underlining, post-it notes, looseleaf pages
    - 1.7 Procedural Rules (d - Final Reports), 1993 - 1995 (Box-folder 14 - 1)
    - 1.8 Staffing of the Tribunal, 1993 - 1996 (Box-folder 14 - 2)
    - 1.9 State Dept. Briefings, 1996 (Box-folder 14 - 3)
      Contains handwritten notes, looseleaf pages,
    - 1.10 Podgers Interview, 1995 - 1996 (Box-folder 14 - 4)
      Contains post-its, notes, markings
    - 1.11 CBC - MacQuarrie, n.d. (Box-folder 14 - 5)
      Handwritten message
    - 1.12 Coalition for International Justice, 1996 (Box-folder 14 - 6)
      Contains handwritten looseleaf notes
    - 2.1 Task Force Report (Box-folder 14 - 7)
      Contains post-it note "Master Copy" &,amp, Monroe Leigh signature
    - 2. 2 Successive Drafts (a) - Proposed Final Draft 21 June 1993 (Box-folder 14 - 8)
      Contains post-it notes, handwritten edits, flags
    - 2. 2 Successive Drafts (b) - Proposed Final Draft t 21 June 1993 (Box-folder 14 - 9)
      Contains memo correspondence, handwritten notes, edits
    - 2.2 Successive Drafts (c) - Proposed Final Draft t 21 June 1993 (Box-folder 15 - 1)
      Contains flags, handwritten notes, edits, correspondence page
    - 2.2 Successive Drafts (d) - Final Draft 30 June 1993 (Box-folder 15 - 2)
      Contains Leigh signature, handwritten edits
    - 2.2 Successive Drafts (e) - Final Draft 5 July 1993 (Box-folder 15 - 3)
      Contains memo correspondence
    - 3.0 Amicus Brief (Box-folder 15 - 4)
      Correspondents include: Monroe Leigh, Mary M. Devlin, Willaim M. Hannay, Jonathan Gluck, contains flags, handwritten notes, post-it notes, penciled edits
    - 4.1 General Correspondence 1993 (Box-folder 15 - 5)
      Correspondents include: Monroe Leigh, Diane F. Orentlicher, Stuart H. Deming, Richard B. Lillich, Larry A. Hammond, Charles R. Norberg, Jeffrey M. Lindy, William Geary, William D. Denson, David A. Martin, John Jay Douglass, Martin C. Loesch, Sushan Demirjian, Contains highlights, Leigh signature, handwritten edits
    - 4.2 General Correspondence 1994 (Box-folder 15 - 6)
      Correspondents include: Monroe Leigh, Allen Ryan, Kenneth B. Reisenfeld, Jay Vogelson, Alaire Bretz Rieffel, Susan Bright, Contains handwritten edits
    - 4.3 General Correspondence 1995 (Box-folder 15 - 7)
      Correspondents include: Monroe Leigh, Marcia Warren, Antonio Cassesse, Douglas Stringer, Peter Lichtenbaum, Mark S. Ellis, Valerie Brion, Susan E. Magalhaes, Robert F. Drinan, Barbara Stone, Richard J. Goldstone, Larry A. Hammond, Stuart H. Deming, Alaire Bretz Rieffel, Jonathan Gluck, Elizabeth R. Rindskopf, Daniel B. Magraw, Jerome J. Shestack, Osborn Maledon, Contains highlights, post-it notes, handwritten edits, memos, Leigh signature, looseleaf pages of notes
    - 4.4 General Correspondence 1996 (Box-folder 16 - 1)
      Correspondents include: Monroe Leigh, Mark J. Hartwig, David N. Lindley, Susan A. Ehrlich, Larry Johnson, David G. Keyko, Hamid Sabi, Anna Ascher, Gonzalo Parra-Aranguren, Mary M. Devlin, Larry A. Hammond, Conrad Harper, Georg Ress, John Heffernan, Barbara Kagan, Michael D. Sandler, Louise Arbour, William Hannay, Sushan Demirjian, John Noyes, Barbara Stone, Contains highlights, looseleaf pages of notes, handwritten notes, post-its, flags, edits
    - 4.5 General Correspondence 1997 (Box-folder 16 - 2)
      Correspondents include: Monroe Leigh, Gabrielle Kirk McDonald, John Heffernan, Nina Bang-Jensen, Valerie Brion, Michael Scharf, Douglas Stringer, Marilou Righini, Alaire Bretz Rieffel, Bob Lutz, J. S. Weigand, Contains handwritten notes, business cards, memos, Leigh signature
    - 4.6 General Correspondence 1998 - 2000 (Box-folder 16 - 3)
      Correspondents include: Monroe Leigh, Gabrielle Kirk McDonald, Willaim Hannay, Gary A. Marek, Professor Mischa Wladimiroff, Adrienne A. Cook, Contains handwritten messages, Leigh signature, annotations
    - 4.7 Goldstone Correspondence, November 1995 - September 1996 (Box-folder 16 - 4)
      Correspondents include: Monroe Leigh, Reid Bauman, Richard J. Goldstone, Barbara Stone, John Heffernan, David Roll, Contains: Leigh signature, handwritten memos, flags
    - 4.8 Letters re Ramadan Gashi, November 1997 - June 1998 (Box-folder 16 - 5)
      Correspondents include: Monroe Leigh, Ramadan Gashi, Gerold W. Libby, John Crook, Louise Arbour, Graham T. Blewitt, Contains: Leigh signature, handwritten notes
    - 4.9 Correspondence with Cristian DeFrancia (Box-folder 16 - 6)
      Correspondents include: Monroe Leigh, Cristian M. DeFrancia, Contains: ICTY application paper "The Use of Anonymous Witnesses in War Crimes Trials: the Legal Background", Cristian M. DeFranica signature
    - 5.1 Indictments (a) - Applications, Hearings and Decisions, 1995 - 1996 (Box-folder 16 - 7)
      Contains photocopies
    - 5.1 Indictments (b) - Indictments, 1995 (Box-folder 16 - 8)
      Contains handwritten notations and comments
    - 5.1 Indictments (c) - Media / Press clippings, 1995 (Box-folder 16 - 9)
      Contains handwritten notations
    - 5.2 Tadic Full Case documents Vol. 1, 1995 (Box-folder 17 - 1)
      Contains post-its, handwritten comments, underlines
    - 5.2.Tadi Full Case documents Vol. 11, 1995 (Box-folder 17 - 2)
    - 5.2.1 Tadic Transcript (Box-folder 17 - 3)
      Contains handwritten memo/notes in middle of Transcript
    - 5.2.2 Tadic Opinion &,amp, Judgment (a), 7 May 1997 (Box-folder 17 - 4)
      Contains post-it notes, handwritten comments, highlights, Monroe Leigh signature
    - 5.2.2 Tadic Opinion &,amp, Judgment (b), 1997 (Box-folder 17 - 5)
      Contains post-it note
    - 5.2.2 Tadic Opinion &,amp, Judgment (c), 1997 (Box-folder 18 - 1)
      Contains post-it notes/markers, handwritten comments
    - 5.2.2 Tadic Opinion &,amp, Judgment (d), 1997 (Box-folder 18 - 2)
      Contains post-it notes/markers, handwritten comments, underlining, 3 1/2 floppy disk labelled "Tadic decision re witnesses"
    - 5.3 Tadic Appeals - Tadic Appellate Decision (ICTY), 1999 (Box-folder 18 - 3)
      Contains tabs
    - 5.3 Tadic Appeals - Decision on the Defence Motion for Interocutory Appeal on Jurisdiction, 1995 (Box-folder 18 - 4)
      Contains post-it markes and pages of handwritten looseleaf comments
    - 6.1 Prosecutor v. Karadzic, 1996 (Box-folder 18 - 5)
      Contains fax message
    - 6.2 In the Matter of the Surrender of Elizaphan Ntakirutimana, 1998 (Box-folder 18 - 6)
      Contains correspondence between Mornoe Leigh and David Stoelting, highlights, pencil comments
    - 7.0 Legal Research (A) Memorandum and Reports, 1972, 1990 - 1999 (Box-folder 19 - 1)
      Contains highlights, notations, edits, post-it note markers
    - 7.0 Legal Research (B) Relevant Court Cases, 1984, 1995, 1997, 2001 (Box-folder 19 - 2)
      Includes: The Queen v. Secretary of State for the Home Department, ex parte: John Gerald Gallagher, Mobil Oil Libya Ltd. V Secretariat of Petroleum and the Governmnet of the Socialist People's Libyan Arab Jamahiriyah, "Tadic, the Anonymous Witness and the Sources of International Procedural Law" by Natasha A. Affolder, "To 'Establish Incredible Events by Credible Evidence': The Use of Affidavit Testimony in Yugoslavia War Crimes Tribunal Proceedings" by Patricia M. Wald
    - 7.0 Legal Research (C) Regina v. Finta decisions and appeals, 1989 - 1994 (Box-folder 19 - 3)
      Contains decisions for Ontario High Court of Justice (06/26/1989, 07/10/1989), Ontario Court of Appeal (04/29/1992), Supreme Court of Canada (03/24/1994), Includes highlights, underlines, post-it markers, post-it notes with notations
    - 8.0 Foreign Sovereign Immunity - Doe v. Karadzic, 1993 - 1995 (Box-folder 19 - 4)
      Contains handwritten notes, memos, business card, newspaper clippings, and proceedings related to Doe v. Karadzic
    - 9.0 Response to Professor Chinkin (A) Relevant Proposals and Cases, 1994 - 1996 (Box-folder 20 - 1)
      Contains checkmarks, handwritten notes,
    - 9.0 Response to Professor Chinkin (B) Background Articles, Briefs, 1994 - 1996 (Box-folder 20 - 2)
      Contains highlights, underlines, checkmarks, handwritten notations, edits
    - 9.0 Response to Professor Chinkin (C) Draft responses, 1996 (Box-folder 20 - 3)
      Contains edits, handwritten notations, post-it note markers
    - 9.0 Response to Professor Chinkin (D) Relevant Constitutional Provisions from individual US States re: Victim's Rights (Box-folder 20 - 4)
      Contains highlights, personal notes, post-it markers,
    - 9.0 Response to Professor Chinkin Vol. II (A) - Article &,amp, Speech Drafts, 1996 - 1997 (Box-folder 20 - 5)
      Contains highlights, underlines, checkmarks, handwritten notations, edits, post-it notes
    - 9.0 Response to Professor Chinkin Vol. II (B) - Correspondence &,amp, Notes, 1995 - 1996 (Box-folder 20 - 6)
      Contains highlights, underlines, checkmarks, handwritten notations, edits, Monroe Leigh signature, Correspondents include: Monroe Leigh, Ted Meron, Detlav Vagts, Ian E. Davidson, Harry Marshall, Stephanos Stavros, Stanislaw Pomorski, David Bederman, Joseph Dellapenna, Daniel G. Partan, Andrew Vollmer, Larry A. Hammond, Stuart Deming, Jonathan Gluck, Jeremy McBride, Mary Devlin, Mark Zaid, David E. Aaronson, Alaire Rieffel, William L. Robinson, Lawrence Collins, Herbert Smith
    - 9.0 Response to Professor Chinkin Vol. II (C) - Press Releases, Articles &,amp, Speeches, multiple dates (Box-folder 21 - 1)
      Contains highlights, underlines, checkmarks, handwritten notations, edits, markers
    - 10.0 In Absentia Trials, Fall 1996 (Box-folder 21 - 2)
      Contains handwriting on copy of "Human Rights Brief" by the Center for Human Rights and Humanitarian Law newsletter, Volume 4, Number 1, Fall 1996
    - 11.0 Law Review Articles, 1988 - 1996 (Box-folder 21 - 3)
      Contains highlights, markings, correspondence, handwritten notes, 1. Bulletin of Human Rights, Special Issue: Fortieth Anniversary of the Universal Declaration of Human Rights, Centre for Human Rights, United Nations, 1988, 2. "Hearsay and the European Court of Human Rights, by Craig Osborne, The Criminal Law Review, 1993, 3. "Constitutional Cooperation" by Henry J. Reske, ABA Journal, October 1996, 4. "Victims and Voyeurs at the Criminal Trial" by Paul Gerwitz, Northwestern Univerisyt Law Review, Spring 1996, 5. "Emphasizing Victims' Rights at the Sentencing Phase of Criminal Proceedings" by Ilana Subar, Maryland Law Review, 1996, 6. "Constitutional Amendment for Crime Victims Urged", The Wall Street Journal, June 26, 1996, 7. "Rule of Law: A Bill of Rights for Crime Victims" by Paul G. Cassell and Steven J. Twist, The Wall Street Journal, April 24, 1996, 8. "Making Amends" Transcript, Online News Hour, PBS, June 25, 1996, 9. "After White v. Illinois: Fundamental Guarantees to a Hollow Right to Confont Witnesses" by Patricia Bennett, Wayne Law Review, 1993
    - 12.0 Anonymous Witnesses (A) - Memorandum / Briefs, 1995 - 1996 (Box-folder 21 - 4)
      Contains post-it notes, highlights, underlines, handwriting, correspondence, thank you card, memorandum re: "The Right of a Defendant to Cross Examine Witnesses against him as articulated in the Senate Legislative History on Article 14 of the International Covenant on Civil and Political Rights", brief on "International jTribunal for the Prosecuction of Persons Responsible for Serious Violations of International Humanitarian Law Committed in the Territory of Former Yugoslavia Since 1991"
    - 12.0 Anonymous Witnesses (B) - Supporting Documents / Articles, 1966 - 1996 (Box-folder 21 - 5)
      Contains highlights, handwritten notes, post-it notes, underlines, government documents from the U.S., Great Britain, New Zealand, Latin America, Japan,
    - 12.0 Anonymous Witnesses (C) - Relevant Cases, 1931 - 1996 (Box-folder 22 - 1)
      Contains intro correspondence, post-it markers, highlights, underlines, handwritten notes on Federal, State, and District court cases
    - 12.0 Anonymous Witnesses (D) - Country Constitutions, 1996 (Box-folder 22 - 2)
    - 13.0 European Court &,amp, Commission on Human Rights cases, 1990 - 1996 (Box-folder 22 - 3)
      Contains cases and articles with highlights, underlines, comments, post-it markers
    - 14.0 Dayton Peace Talks, 1995 - 1996 (Box-folder 22 - 4)
      Contains articles and summaries with highlights, underlines, comments, looseleaf paper notes, post-it markers, Monroe Leigh signature
    - 15.0 Serb Reports of War Crimes, 1996 (Box-folder 23 - 1)
      Contains correspondence with Vladislav Jovanovic, summaries and reports
    - 16.0 Meeting with Justice Louise Arbour, 1996 (Box-folder 23 - 2)
      Contains correspondence with John W Heffernan, Thomas Warrick, Mark Levine, Monroe Leigh, handwritten notes,
    - 17.1 Stringer Letter to Lutz 11 February 1997 (Box-folder 23 - 3)
      Contains correspondence with Professor Robert Lutz, Douglas Stringer, Monroe Leigh, Stuart Deming, references Human Rights cases and gives summaries
    - 17.2 ABA Year in Review, 1997 (Box-folder 23 - 4)
      Contains handwritten notes, correspondence with Maury D. Shenk, Monroe Leigh, Michael Scharf, Joseph F. Murphy, post-it notes, business card, and notations
    - 18.0 Articles on Criminal Sanctions and Truth Commissions, 1991 - 1998 (Box-folder 23 - 5)
      Contains hadnwritten notes, highlights, post-it notes, newspaper clippings
    - 18.2 Implementing Legislation - US - Elizaphan Case, 1997 - 1998 (Box-folder 23 - 6)
    - 19.0 20th Century Fund, 1998 (Box-folder 23 - 7)
      Contains correspondence with Nina Bang-Jensen, Kelly Goss, and Monroe Leigh
    - 20.0 Kosovo - Doherty Report 1998 (Box-folder 23 - 8)
      Contains handwritten memo, correspondence with Maury D. Shenk, Monroe Leigh, Kevin A. Doherty
    - Report to the Chairman, Committee on Foreign Relations, U.S. Senate: Former Yugoslavia, War Crimes Truibunal's Workload Exceeds Capacity (GAO/NSIAD-98-134), June 1998 (Box-folder 23 - 9)
    - Report: The Prosecutor v. Slobodan Milosevic et al., Case No. IT-99-37-I (ICTY), 1999 (Box-folder 24 - 1)
      Contains correspondence with David Stoelting and Monroe Leigh, Presentation of an Indictment for Review and Application for Warrants of Arrest and for Related Orders, Indictment, Decision on Review of Indictment and Application for Consequential Orders, Statement by Justice Arbour
    - Report: Bringing War Criminals to Justice: Obligations, Options, Recommendations by the Public International Law and Policy Group, Balkan Institute, and University of Dayton, 1997 (Box-folder 24 - 2)
      Contains letter from Paul R. Williams
    - Report of the Century Foundation / Twentieth Century Fund Task Force on Apprehending Indicted War Criminals: Making Justice Work, 1998 (Box-folder 24 - 3)
      Contains Monroe Leigh signature
    - Report on the International Tribunal to Adjudicate War Crimes Committed in Former Yugoslavia, July 8, 1993. AUTHORITIES Volume I (A), 1994 (Box-folder 24 - 4)
      Contains index of authorities 1 - 9 (US Federal cases) related to War Crimes Adjudication, prepared by ABA Section of International Law and Practice: M. Leigh, P. Bloodgood, S. Deming, E. Echols
    - Report on the International Tribunal to Adjudicate War Crimes Committed in Former Yugoslavia, July 8, 1993. AUTHORITIES Volume I (B), 1994 (Box-folder 24 - 5)
      Contains index of authorities 10 - 16 (US Federal cases) related to War Crimes Adjudication, prepared by ABA Section of International Law and Practice: M. Leigh, P. Bloodgood, S. Deming, E. Echols
    - Report on the International Tribunal to Adjudicate War Crimes Committed in Former Yugoslavia, July 8, 1993. AUTHORITIES Volume I (C), 1994 (Box-folder 24 - 6)
      Contains index of authorities 17 - 25 (US Federal cases) related to War Crimes Adjudication, prepared by ABA Section of International Law and Practice: M. Leigh, P. Bloodgood, S. Deming, E. Echols
    - Report on the International Tribunal to Adjudicate War Crimes Committed in Former Yugoslavia, July 8, 1993. AUTHORITIES Volume II (A), 1994 (Box-folder 24 - 7)
      Contains index of authorities 26 - 33 (International court cases, Tribunal materials, ABA materials) related to War Crimes Adjudication with highlights, underlines, and post-it markers, prepared by ABA Section of International Law and Practice: M. Leigh, P. Bloodgood, S. Deming, E. Echols
    - Report on the International Tribunal to Adjudicate War Crimes Committed in Former Yugoslavia, July 8, 1993. AUTHORITIES Volume II (B), 1994 (Box-folder 25 - 1)
      Contains index of authorities 34 - 42 (UN materials) related to War Crimes Adjudication with highlights, underlines, and post-it markers, prepared by ABA Section of International Law and Practice: M. Leigh, P. Bloodgood, S. Deming, E. Echols
    - Report on the International Tribunal to Adjudicate War Crimes Committed in Former Yugoslavia, July 8, 1993. AUTHORITIES Volume II (C), 1994 (Box-folder 25 - 2)
      Contains index of authorities 43 - 50 (International Agreements, Charters and Treaties) related to War Crimes Adjudication with highlights, underlines, and post-it markers, prepared by ABA Section of International Law and Practice: M. Leigh, P. Bloodgood, S. Deming, E. Echols
    - Report on the International Tribunal to Adjudicate War Crimes Committed in Former Yugoslavia, July 8, 1993. AUTHORITIES Volume III (A), 1994 (Box-folder 25 - 3)
      Contains index of authorities 51 - 60 (International statutes, US Legislative - Federal statutes, US Legislative - State statutes, US Legislative History) related to War Crimes Adjudication with highlights, prepared by ABA Section of International Law and Practice: M. Leigh, P. Bloodgood, S. Deming, E. Echols
    - Report on the International Tribunal to Adjudicate War Crimes Committed in Former Yugoslavia, July 8, 1993. AUTHORITIES Volume III (B), 1994 (Box-folder 25 - 4)
      Contains index of authorities 61 - 75 (Books, Articles &,amp, Pamphlets) related to War Crimes Adjudication with highlights, prepared by ABA Section of International Law and Practice: M. Leigh, P. Bloodgood, S. Deming, E. Echols
    - Report on the International Tribunal to Adjudicate War Crimes Committed in Former Yugoslavia, July 8, 1993. AUTHORITIES Volume IV (A), 1994 (Box-folder 25 - 5)
      Contains index of authorities 76 - 85 (Books, Articles, Pamphlets, Statements, Addresses &,amp, Press Releases, Miscellaneous) related to War Crimes Adjudication, prepared by ABA section of International Law and Practice: M. Leigh, P. Bloodgood, S. Deming, E. Echols
    - Report on the International Tribunal to Adjudicate War Crimes Committed in Former Yugoslavia, July 8, 1993. AUTHORITIES Volume IV (B), 1994 (Box-folder 25 - 6)
      Contains index of authorities 86 - 93 (Books, Articles, Pamphlets, Statements, Addresses &,amp, Press Releases, Miscellaneous) related to War Crimes Adjudication, prepared by ABA section of International Law and Practice: M. Leigh, P. Bloodgood, S. Deming, E. Echols
    - Articles re: Task Force on War Crimes in Yugoslavia, 1997 (Box-folder 26 - 1)
      Contains letter from Inman Deming to Monroe Leigh, "The Year In Review: International Criminal Tribunal for the Former Yugoslavia" by Douglas Stringer, "After White v. Illinois: Fundamental Guarantees to a Hollow Right to Confront Witnessess" by Patricia W. Bennett, "The Predicament of Peacekeeping in Bosnia" by Tibor Varady
    - UN Security Council: Letter Dated 24 May 1994 from the Secretary - General to the President of the Security Council, S/1994/674, 27 May 1994 (Box-folder 26 - 2)
      Contains highlights
    - Congressional Resolutions re: NATO, Kosovo, Yugoslavia, 1999 (Box-folder 26 - 3)
      Includes copies of following resolutions: H. Con. Res. 42, S. J. Res. 20, H. Res. 1368, H. Res. 103, S. J. Res. 12, H. Con. Res. 29, H. R. 647, S. 720
    - Treaty Interpretation, the Constitution and the Rule of Law" by John Norton Moore, 15 November 2000 (Box-folder 26 - 4)
      Contains letter from John Norton Moore to Monroe Leigh
    - Kostovski v. Netherlands Criminal Proceedings, anonymous witnesses (Series A, No 166 Application No 11454/85), 20 November 1989 (Box-folder 26 - 5)
    - Looseleaf Notes re: Verdict and Appeal, [1997?] (Box-folder 26 - 6)
      Contains handwritten notes on sheets of looseleaf
    - Monroe Leigh Notebooks Vol. 1, including Index [1993] (Box-folder 26 - 7)